And that there'd be an asterisk by his name
because he'd be a cyborg.
So you got a little competition.
I really don't see what the big deal is.
(Sheldon:)Of course you don't.
You've never excelled at anything.
(Penny:)I don't understand, exactly how did
he get any friends in the first place?
(Howard:)We liked Leonard.
What are you gonna do, just give up?
Yes, it's what a rational person does
when his entire life's work is invalidated...
(Sheldon:)...by a postpubescent Asian wunderkind.
(Sheldon:)He ceases his fruitless efforts,
he donates his body to scientific research...
(Sheldon:)...and he waits to die.
(Penny:)I'm confused again. Is he waiting, or do
we get to shoot him between the eyes?
(Penny(opening door):)- Hey.
- Hey.
(Sheldon:)I've decided you're right.
(Sheldon:)- My career is not over.
- Great.
But since Dennis Kim
has rendered my research pointless...
(Sheldon:)...I just have to find
something else to focus on.